<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>EMMA XIE</title>
    <description>Write an awesome description for your new site here. You can edit this line in _config.yml. It will appear in your document head meta (for Google search results) and in your feed.xml site description.
</description>
    <link>http://yourdomain.com/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://yourdomain.com/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Sun, 15 May 2016 17:36:04 -0400</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 15 May 2016 17:36:04 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v3.0.1</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>Hello World!</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;category category--full&quot;&gt;Nutrition&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 class=&quot;title title--full&quot;&gt;What Goes Around Comes Around&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;meta__date&quot;&gt; 6 Apr&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Primitive man is known to us by the stages of development through which he has passed: that is, through the inanimate monuments and implements which he has left behind for us, through our knowledge of his art, his religion and his attitude towards life, which we have received either directly or through the medium of legends, myths and fairy tales; and through the remnants of his ways of thinking that survive in our own manners and customs.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Moreover, in a certain sense he is still our contemporary: there are people whom we still consider more closely related to primitive man than to ourselves, in whom we therefore recognize the direct descendants and representatives of earlier man. We can thus judge the so-called savage and semi-savage races; their psychic life assumes a peculiar interest for us, for we can recognize in their psychic life a well-preserved, early stage of our own development.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The aborigines of Australia are looked upon as a peculiar race which shows neither physical nor linguistic relationship with its nearest neighbours, the Melanesian, Polynesian and Malayan races. They do not build houses or permanent huts; they do not cultivate the soil or keep any domestic animals except dogs; and they do not even know the art of pottery. They live exclusively on the flesh of all sorts of animals which they kill in the chase, and on the roots which they dig. Kings or chieftains are unknown among them, and all communal affairs are decided by the elders in assembly. It is quite doubtful whether they evince any traces of religion in the form of worship of higher beings. The tribes living in the interior who have to contend with the greatest vicissitudes of life owing to a scarcity of water, seem in every way more primitive than those who live near the coast.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If I judge my readers’ impressions correctly, I dare say that after hearing all that was said about taboo they are far from knowing what to understand by it and where to store it in their minds. This is surely due to the insufficient information I have given and to the omission of all discussions concerning the relation of taboo to superstition, to belief in the soul, and to religion. On the other hand I fear that a more detailed description of what is known about taboo would be still more confusing; I can therefore assure the reader that the state of affairs is really far from clear. We may say, however, that we deal with a series of restrictions which these primitive races impose upon themselves; this and that is forbidden without any apparent reason; nor does it occur to them to question this matter, for they subject themselves to these restrictions as a matter of course and are convinced that any transgression will be punished automatically in the most severe manner. There are reliable reports that innocent transgressions of such prohibitions have actually been punished automatically. For instance, the innocent offender who had eaten from a forbidden animal became deeply depressed, expected his death and then actually died. The prohibitions mostly concern matters which are capable of enjoyment such as freedom of movement and unrestrained intercourse; in some cases they appear very ingenious, evidently representing abstinences and renunciations; in other cases their content is quite incomprehensible, they seem to concern themselves with trifles and give the impression of ceremonials. Something like a theory seems to underlie all these prohibitions, it seems as if these prohibitions are necessary because some persons and objects possess a dangerous power which is transmitted by contact with the object so charged, almost like a contagion. The quantity of this dangerous property is also taken into consideration. Some persons or things have more of it than others and the danger is precisely in accordance with the charge. The most peculiar part of it is that any one who has violated such a prohibition assumes the nature of the forbidden object as if he had absorbed the whole dangerous charge. This power is inherent in all persons who are more or less prominent, such as kings, priests and the newly born, in all exceptional physical states such as menstruation, puberty and birth, in everything sinister like illness and death and in everything connected with these conditions by virtue of contagion or dissemination.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;First of all it must be said that it is useless to question savages as to the real motivation of their prohibitions or as to the genesis of taboo. According to our assumption they must be incapable of telling us anything about it since this motivation is ‘unconscious’ to them. But following the model of the compulsive prohibition we shall construct the history of taboo as follows: Taboos are very ancient prohibitions which at one time were forced upon a generation of primitive people from without, that is, they probably were forcibly impressed upon them by an earlier generation. These prohibitions concerned actions for which there existed a strong desire. The prohibitions maintained themselves from generation to generation, perhaps only as the result of a tradition set up by paternal and social authority. But in later generations they have perhaps already become ‘organized’ as a piece of inherited psychic property. Whether there are such ‘innate ideas’ or whether these have brought about the fixation of the taboo by themselves or by co-operating with education no one could decide in the particular case in question. The persistence of taboo teaches, however, one thing, namely, that the original pleasure to do the forbidden still continues among taboo races. They therefore assume an &lt;em&gt;ambivalent attitude&lt;/em&gt; toward their taboo prohibitions; in their unconscious they would like nothing better than to transgress them but they are also afraid to do it; they are afraid just because they would like to transgress, and the fear is stronger than the pleasure. But in every individual of the race the desire for it is unconscious, just as in the neurotic.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It seems like an obvious contradiction that persons of such perfection of power should themselves require the greatest care to guard them against threatening dangers, but this is not the only contradiction revealed in the treatment of royal persons on the part of savages. These races consider it necessary to watch over their kings to see that they use their powers in the right way; they are by no means sure of their good intentions or of their conscientiousness. A strain of mistrust is mingled with the motivation of the taboo rules for the king. “The idea that early kingdoms are despotisms”, says Frazer[59], “in which the people exist only for the sovereign, is wholly inapplicable to the monarchies we are considering. On the contrary, the sovereign in them exists only for his subjects: his life is only valuable so long as he discharges the duties of his position by ordering the course of nature for his people’s benefit. So soon as he fails to do so, the care, the devotion, the religious homage which they had hitherto lavished on him cease and are changed into hatred and contempt; he is ignominiously dismissed and may be thankful if he escapes with his life. Worshipped as a god one day, he is killed as a criminal the next. But in this changed behaviour of the people there is nothing capricious or inconsistent. On the contrary, their conduct is quite consistent. If their king is their god he is or should be, also their preserver; and if he will not preserve them he must make room for another who will. So long, however, as he answers their expectations, there is no limit to the care which they take of him, and which they compel him to take of himself. A king of this sort lives hedged in by ceremonious etiquette, a network of prohibitions and observances, of which the intention is not to contribute to his dignity, much less to his comfort, but to restrain him from conduct which, by disturbing the harmony of nature, might involve himself, his people, and the universe in one common catastrophe. Far from adding to his comfort, these observances, by trammelling his every act, annihilate his freedom and often render the very life, which it is their object to preserve, a burden and sorrow to him.”&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
Excerpts from &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.gutenberg.org/ebooks/41214&quot;&gt;Totem and Taboo&lt;/a&gt; by Sigmund Freud.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 29 Apr 2016 14:05:49 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://yourdomain.com/blog/blog1.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://yourdomain.com/blog/blog1.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>blog</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Wirkn</title>
        <description>&lt;div class=&quot;description&quot;&gt;
	&lt;header class=&quot;post-header&quot;&gt;
    &lt;h1 class=&quot;post-title&quot; itemprop=&quot;name headline&quot;&gt;Wirkn&lt;/h1&gt;
  &lt;/header&gt;
	&lt;div class=&quot;details&quot;&gt;
		Marketing design, print media, branding design, web-development
		&lt;br /&gt;
		Jan 2015-August 2015
		&lt;br /&gt;
		Programs: various
		&lt;br /&gt;
	&lt;/div&gt;
Wirkn is a mobile app startup from the heart of Toronto that provides an alternative to job search with video applications. My projects include creating general branding promotional graphics, Google and Facebook ads, hiring ads for our connected employers, social media content, newsletter design, and infographics.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;www.wirkn.com&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Wirkn Website&lt;/a&gt;

&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;images&quot;&gt;
	&lt;img src=&quot;http://orig12.deviantart.net/5fe6/f/2015/202/1/9/1_by_eexie-d927va2.png&quot; /&gt;
	&lt;img src=&quot;http://orig00.deviantart.net/0364/f/2015/202/2/d/2_by_eexie-d927v2a.png&quot; /&gt;
	&lt;img src=&quot;http://orig15.deviantart.net/b0d6/f/2015/208/9/a/3_by_eexie-d9311cf.png&quot; /&gt;
	&lt;img src=&quot;http://orig02.deviantart.net/cd40/f/2015/202/4/0/3_by_eexie-d927tky.png&quot; /&gt;
	&lt;img src=&quot;http://orig08.deviantart.net/439e/f/2015/202/9/f/4_by_eexie-d927sk0.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;!-- 
&lt;figure class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code class=&quot;language-ruby&quot; data-lang=&quot;ruby&quot;&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;k&quot;&gt;def&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;nf&quot;&gt;print_hi&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;(&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;nb&quot;&gt;name&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;)&lt;/span&gt;
  &lt;span class=&quot;nb&quot;&gt;puts&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;s2&quot;&gt;&quot;Hi, &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;si&quot;&gt;#{&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;nb&quot;&gt;name&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;si&quot;&gt;}&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;s2&quot;&gt;&quot;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class=&quot;k&quot;&gt;end&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;print_hi&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;(&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;s1&quot;&gt;&#39;Tom&#39;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;)&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class=&quot;c1&quot;&gt;#=&amp;gt; prints &#39;Hi, Tom&#39; to STDOUT.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;
 --&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 18 Feb 2016 13:05:49 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://yourdomain.com/design/w.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://yourdomain.com/design/w.html</guid>
        
        <category>branding &amp; UX</category>
        
        
        <category>design</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Stag</title>
        <description>&lt;div class=&quot;description&quot;&gt;
	&lt;header class=&quot;post-header&quot;&gt;
    &lt;h1 class=&quot;post-title&quot; itemprop=&quot;name headline&quot;&gt;The Stag&lt;/h1&gt;
  &lt;/header&gt;
	&lt;div class=&quot;details&quot;&gt;
		Digital Illustration
		&lt;br /&gt;
		February 2014
		&lt;br /&gt;
		Programs: Adobe Illustrator
		&lt;br /&gt;
		Dimensions: 11&quot; x 17&quot;
		&lt;br /&gt;
	&lt;/div&gt;
A vector illustration of Will Graham from NBC&#39;s Hannibal.


&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;images&quot;&gt;
	&lt;img src=&quot;http://fc07.deviantart.net/fs70/f/2014/088/3/a/the_stag_by_eexie-d7c55aw.jpg&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;!-- 
&lt;figure class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code class=&quot;language-ruby&quot; data-lang=&quot;ruby&quot;&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;k&quot;&gt;def&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;nf&quot;&gt;print_hi&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;(&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;nb&quot;&gt;name&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;)&lt;/span&gt;
  &lt;span class=&quot;nb&quot;&gt;puts&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;s2&quot;&gt;&quot;Hi, &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;si&quot;&gt;#{&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;nb&quot;&gt;name&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;si&quot;&gt;}&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;s2&quot;&gt;&quot;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class=&quot;k&quot;&gt;end&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;print_hi&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;(&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;s1&quot;&gt;&#39;Tom&#39;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;)&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class=&quot;c1&quot;&gt;#=&amp;gt; prints &#39;Hi, Tom&#39; to STDOUT.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;
 --&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 18 Feb 2016 13:05:49 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://yourdomain.com/art/stag.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://yourdomain.com/art/stag.html</guid>
        
        <category>digital illustration</category>
        
        
        <category>art</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Sammy&#39;s Story</title>
        <description>&lt;div class=&quot;description&quot;&gt;
	&lt;header class=&quot;post-header&quot;&gt;
    &lt;h1 class=&quot;post-title&quot; itemprop=&quot;name headline&quot;&gt;Sammy&#39;s Story&lt;/h1&gt;
  &lt;/header&gt;
	&lt;div class=&quot;details&quot;&gt;
		Kinetic Typography, Animation
		&lt;br /&gt;
		May 2013 - June 2013
		&lt;br /&gt;
		Programs: Adobe After Effects, Illustrator
		&lt;br /&gt;
		Size: 1080p
		&lt;br /&gt;
	&lt;/div&gt;
A short 1-minute kinetic typography video animated to my favourite quote from my favourite movie, Nolan&#39;s 2001 film &quot;Memento.&quot;


&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;images&quot;&gt;
	&lt;iframe width=&quot;100%&quot; height=&quot;500&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/ORbCdc35G6E&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;
	&lt;img src=&quot;http://orig02.deviantart.net/a951/f/2016/081/3/2/cover_by_eexie-d9w2n56.png&quot; /&gt;
	&lt;img src=&quot;http://pre00.deviantart.net/0318/th/pre/i/2016/081/3/8/cover_by_eexie-d9w2o8g.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;!-- 
&lt;figure class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code class=&quot;language-ruby&quot; data-lang=&quot;ruby&quot;&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;k&quot;&gt;def&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;nf&quot;&gt;print_hi&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;(&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;nb&quot;&gt;name&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;)&lt;/span&gt;
  &lt;span class=&quot;nb&quot;&gt;puts&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;s2&quot;&gt;&quot;Hi, &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;si&quot;&gt;#{&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;nb&quot;&gt;name&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;si&quot;&gt;}&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;s2&quot;&gt;&quot;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class=&quot;k&quot;&gt;end&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;print_hi&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;(&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;s1&quot;&gt;&#39;Tom&#39;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;)&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class=&quot;c1&quot;&gt;#=&amp;gt; prints &#39;Hi, Tom&#39; to STDOUT.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;
 --&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 18 Feb 2016 13:05:49 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://yourdomain.com/art/sammy.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://yourdomain.com/art/sammy.html</guid>
        
        <category>kinetic typography</category>
        
        
        <category>art</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Nickel</title>
        <description>&lt;div class=&quot;description&quot;&gt;
	&lt;header class=&quot;post-header&quot;&gt;
    &lt;h1 class=&quot;post-title&quot; itemprop=&quot;name headline&quot;&gt;Nickel&lt;/h1&gt;
  &lt;/header&gt;
	&lt;div class=&quot;details&quot;&gt;
		Mixed Media
		&lt;br /&gt;
		January 2015
		&lt;br /&gt;
		Materials: Plexiglass, acrylic, watercolour, ink, charcoal
		&lt;br /&gt;
		Dimensions: 25&quot; x 25&quot;
		&lt;br /&gt;
	&lt;/div&gt;
A plexiglass piece inspired by &quot;If I Had a Nickel&quot; by B.J. Novak, from his debut novel &quot;One More Thing&quot;


&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;images&quot;&gt;
	&lt;img src=&quot;http://orig13.deviantart.net/ff79/f/2016/081/f/f/cover_by_eexie-d9w2s8k.jpg&quot; /&gt;
	&lt;img src=&quot;http://orig13.deviantart.net/5ed3/f/2015/015/3/0/n2_by_eexie-d8e1ixa.jpg&quot; /&gt;
	&lt;img src=&quot;http://orig07.deviantart.net/bef7/f/2015/015/0/6/n1_by_eexie-d8e1iy5.jpg&quot; /&gt;
	&lt;img src=&quot;http://orig03.deviantart.net/a8e3/f/2015/015/d/b/n3_by_eexie-d8e1kac.jpg&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;!-- 
&lt;figure class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code class=&quot;language-ruby&quot; data-lang=&quot;ruby&quot;&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;k&quot;&gt;def&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;nf&quot;&gt;print_hi&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;(&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;nb&quot;&gt;name&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;)&lt;/span&gt;
  &lt;span class=&quot;nb&quot;&gt;puts&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;s2&quot;&gt;&quot;Hi, &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;si&quot;&gt;#{&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;nb&quot;&gt;name&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;si&quot;&gt;}&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;s2&quot;&gt;&quot;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class=&quot;k&quot;&gt;end&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;print_hi&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;(&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;s1&quot;&gt;&#39;Tom&#39;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;)&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class=&quot;c1&quot;&gt;#=&amp;gt; prints &#39;Hi, Tom&#39; to STDOUT.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;
 --&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 18 Feb 2016 13:05:49 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://yourdomain.com/art/nickel.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://yourdomain.com/art/nickel.html</guid>
        
        <category>mixed media</category>
        
        
        <category>art</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Good Morning</title>
        <description>&lt;div class=&quot;description&quot;&gt;
	&lt;header class=&quot;post-header&quot;&gt;
    &lt;h1 class=&quot;post-title&quot; itemprop=&quot;name headline&quot;&gt;Good Morning&lt;/h1&gt;
  &lt;/header&gt;
	&lt;div class=&quot;details&quot;&gt;
		Mixed Media Illustration
		&lt;br /&gt;
		June 2013
		&lt;br /&gt;
		Materials: Watercolour, ink, oil pastels
		&lt;br /&gt;
		Dimensions: 18&quot; x 24&quot;
		&lt;br /&gt;
	&lt;/div&gt;
Self portrait inspired by the song &quot;A Day in the Life&quot; by The Beatles


&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;images&quot;&gt;
	&lt;img src=&quot;http://orig00.deviantart.net/64d5/f/2013/152/7/3/good_morning_by_xrabbii_luvx-d67gchm.jpg&quot; /&gt;
	&lt;img src=&quot;http://orig00.deviantart.net/9f7f/f/2013/152/c/a/_good_morning__details_ii_by_xrabbii_luvx-d67gczd.jpg&quot; /&gt;
	&lt;img src=&quot;http://orig13.deviantart.net/5f56/f/2013/152/1/c/_good_morning__details_i_by_xrabbii_luvx-d67gcsz.jpg&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;!-- 
&lt;figure class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code class=&quot;language-ruby&quot; data-lang=&quot;ruby&quot;&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;k&quot;&gt;def&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;nf&quot;&gt;print_hi&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;(&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;nb&quot;&gt;name&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;)&lt;/span&gt;
  &lt;span class=&quot;nb&quot;&gt;puts&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;s2&quot;&gt;&quot;Hi, &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;si&quot;&gt;#{&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;nb&quot;&gt;name&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;si&quot;&gt;}&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;s2&quot;&gt;&quot;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class=&quot;k&quot;&gt;end&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;print_hi&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;(&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;s1&quot;&gt;&#39;Tom&#39;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;)&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class=&quot;c1&quot;&gt;#=&amp;gt; prints &#39;Hi, Tom&#39; to STDOUT.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;
 --&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 18 Feb 2016 13:05:49 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://yourdomain.com/art/morning.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://yourdomain.com/art/morning.html</guid>
        
        <category>traditional illustration</category>
        
        
        <category>art</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Miscellaneous</title>
        <description>&lt;div class=&quot;description&quot;&gt;
	&lt;header class=&quot;post-header&quot;&gt;
    &lt;h1 class=&quot;post-title&quot; itemprop=&quot;name headline&quot;&gt;Miscellaneous&lt;/h1&gt;
  &lt;/header&gt;
	&lt;div class=&quot;details&quot;&gt;
		2011-Present
		&lt;br /&gt;
		Programs &amp;amp; Materials: various
		&lt;br /&gt;
	&lt;/div&gt;
A small collection of pieces from my sketchbook and other miscellaneous work over the past years.


&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;images&quot;&gt;
	&lt;img src=&quot;http://orig08.deviantart.net/cee4/f/2014/060/b/0/sneaks_by_xexultau-d78gjfv.jpg&quot; /&gt;
	&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Scratchboard piece of my sneakers&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
	&lt;img src=&quot;http://orig00.deviantart.net/1fe8/f/2016/083/4/4/cover_by_eexie-d9w9k82.jpg&quot; /&gt;
	&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Sketchbook study of stamps and cutouts&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
	&lt;img src=&quot;http://orig00.deviantart.net/896e/f/2013/152/6/3/life_of_a_flower_by_xrabbii_luvx-d67giud.jpg&quot; /&gt;
	&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Still life study of the &quot;life&quot; of an origami flower&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
	&lt;img src=&quot;http://other00.deviantart.net/daa2/o/2014/201/a/6/a6dfc077bbe5314db379ae4b5077f3aa.png&quot; /&gt;
	&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Trivia Club promotional poster&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
	&lt;img src=&quot;http://orig11.deviantart.net/25f8/f/2015/203/4/8/3_by_eexie-d92c67y.png&quot; /&gt;
	&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Posters for my 2014-2015 Student Council election campaign&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;!-- 
&lt;figure class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code class=&quot;language-ruby&quot; data-lang=&quot;ruby&quot;&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;k&quot;&gt;def&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;nf&quot;&gt;print_hi&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;(&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;nb&quot;&gt;name&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;)&lt;/span&gt;
  &lt;span class=&quot;nb&quot;&gt;puts&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;s2&quot;&gt;&quot;Hi, &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;si&quot;&gt;#{&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;nb&quot;&gt;name&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;si&quot;&gt;}&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;s2&quot;&gt;&quot;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class=&quot;k&quot;&gt;end&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;print_hi&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;(&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;s1&quot;&gt;&#39;Tom&#39;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;)&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class=&quot;c1&quot;&gt;#=&amp;gt; prints &#39;Hi, Tom&#39; to STDOUT.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;
 --&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 18 Feb 2016 13:05:49 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://yourdomain.com/art/misc.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://yourdomain.com/art/misc.html</guid>
        
        <category>studies &amp; minor projects</category>
        
        
        <category>art</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>If Your Love Isn&#39;t Strong</title>
        <description>&lt;div class=&quot;description&quot;&gt;
	&lt;header class=&quot;post-header&quot;&gt;
    &lt;h1 class=&quot;post-title&quot; itemprop=&quot;name headline&quot;&gt;If Your Love Isn&#39;t Strong&lt;/h1&gt;
  &lt;/header&gt;
	&lt;div class=&quot;details&quot;&gt;
		Digital Illustration
		&lt;br /&gt;
		January 2014
		&lt;br /&gt;
		Programs: Paint Tool Sai
		&lt;br /&gt;
	&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;&quot;Take me back
&lt;br /&gt;Give it up, give it up to me
&lt;br /&gt;Cause I can&#39;t go on
&lt;br /&gt;If your love isn&#39;t strong&quot;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
Painting of Danielle Haim from the band Haim.


&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;images&quot;&gt;
	&lt;img src=&quot;http://orig11.deviantart.net/91b3/f/2014/032/2/c/if_your_love_isn_t_strong_by_xexultau-d74ldl7.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;!-- 
&lt;figure class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code class=&quot;language-ruby&quot; data-lang=&quot;ruby&quot;&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;k&quot;&gt;def&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;nf&quot;&gt;print_hi&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;(&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;nb&quot;&gt;name&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;)&lt;/span&gt;
  &lt;span class=&quot;nb&quot;&gt;puts&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;s2&quot;&gt;&quot;Hi, &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;si&quot;&gt;#{&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;nb&quot;&gt;name&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;si&quot;&gt;}&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;s2&quot;&gt;&quot;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class=&quot;k&quot;&gt;end&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;print_hi&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;(&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;s1&quot;&gt;&#39;Tom&#39;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;)&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class=&quot;c1&quot;&gt;#=&amp;gt; prints &#39;Hi, Tom&#39; to STDOUT.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;
 --&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 18 Feb 2016 13:05:49 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://yourdomain.com/art/haim.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://yourdomain.com/art/haim.html</guid>
        
        <category>digital illustration</category>
        
        
        <category>art</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Something Fish-y</title>
        <description>&lt;div class=&quot;description&quot;&gt;
	&lt;header class=&quot;post-header&quot;&gt;
    &lt;h1 class=&quot;post-title&quot; itemprop=&quot;name headline&quot;&gt;Something Fish-y&lt;/h1&gt;
  &lt;/header&gt;
	&lt;div class=&quot;details&quot;&gt;
		June 2013
		&lt;br /&gt;
		Materials: Rice paper, wire, candle wax, tissue paper, lighting kit
		&lt;br /&gt;
	&lt;/div&gt;
A lighting fixture that exists in two states.


&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;images&quot;&gt;
	&lt;img src=&quot;http://orig09.deviantart.net/549e/f/2013/155/e/f/something_fish_y_by_xrabbii_luvx-d67ujw7.png&quot; /&gt;
	&lt;img src=&quot;http://orig02.deviantart.net/867e/f/2013/155/1/a/fish_y_detail_i_by_xrabbii_luvx-d67ujqg.jpg&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;!-- 
&lt;figure class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code class=&quot;language-ruby&quot; data-lang=&quot;ruby&quot;&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;k&quot;&gt;def&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;nf&quot;&gt;print_hi&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;(&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;nb&quot;&gt;name&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;)&lt;/span&gt;
  &lt;span class=&quot;nb&quot;&gt;puts&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;s2&quot;&gt;&quot;Hi, &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;si&quot;&gt;#{&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;nb&quot;&gt;name&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;si&quot;&gt;}&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;s2&quot;&gt;&quot;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class=&quot;k&quot;&gt;end&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;print_hi&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;(&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;s1&quot;&gt;&#39;Tom&#39;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;)&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class=&quot;c1&quot;&gt;#=&amp;gt; prints &#39;Hi, Tom&#39; to STDOUT.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;
 --&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 18 Feb 2016 13:05:49 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://yourdomain.com/art/fish-y.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://yourdomain.com/art/fish-y.html</guid>
        
        <category>lighting design</category>
        
        
        <category>art</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Burgerlar</title>
        <description>&lt;div class=&quot;description&quot;&gt;
	&lt;header class=&quot;post-header&quot;&gt;
    &lt;h1 class=&quot;post-title&quot; itemprop=&quot;name headline&quot;&gt;The Burgerlar&lt;/h1&gt;
  &lt;/header&gt;
	&lt;div class=&quot;details&quot;&gt;
		Mixed Media Illustration
		&lt;br /&gt;
		May 2014
		&lt;br /&gt;
		Materials: Watercolour, acrylic, pen, ink
		&lt;br /&gt;
		Dimensions: 20&quot; x 28&quot;
		&lt;br /&gt;
	&lt;/div&gt;
A burglar + a burger.


&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;images&quot;&gt;
	&lt;img src=&quot;http://fc04.deviantart.net/fs71/f/2014/153/c/1/dun_worry_it_s_ketchup_by_eexie-d7kqlvv.jpg&quot; /&gt;
	&lt;img src=&quot;http://orig13.deviantart.net/0700/f/2014/153/c/3/dunworryitsketchup_details_by_eexie-d7kqmcj.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;!-- 
&lt;figure class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code class=&quot;language-ruby&quot; data-lang=&quot;ruby&quot;&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;k&quot;&gt;def&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;nf&quot;&gt;print_hi&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;(&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;nb&quot;&gt;name&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;)&lt;/span&gt;
  &lt;span class=&quot;nb&quot;&gt;puts&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;s2&quot;&gt;&quot;Hi, &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;si&quot;&gt;#{&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;nb&quot;&gt;name&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;si&quot;&gt;}&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;s2&quot;&gt;&quot;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class=&quot;k&quot;&gt;end&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;print_hi&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;(&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;s1&quot;&gt;&#39;Tom&#39;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;)&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class=&quot;c1&quot;&gt;#=&amp;gt; prints &#39;Hi, Tom&#39; to STDOUT.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;
 --&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 18 Feb 2016 13:05:49 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://yourdomain.com/art/burgerlar.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://yourdomain.com/art/burgerlar.html</guid>
        
        <category>traditional illustration</category>
        
        
        <category>art</category>
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
